Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. This is not
an artificial intelligence. I feel like
I need to say that before the episode
that you know I'm a real person doing
these videos, but I want to show you how
we're using AI to create just some
incredible content. Um, and how we're
using it as well for advertising and
things like that.
The the main thing is is that
um artificial intelligence AI videos
have taken a quantum leap over the last
weekend and in the last 6 months they
have just massively improved. So I'm
going to kind of take you through a
journey. We're going to end up and I'm
going to show you using the tool that
I've been using a lot called uh Sora
right here. Let me let me add my uh my
display name right there. or Jeremiah
Kowski. Okay, great. So, Sora, look at I
I created these videos using Sora with
my face
um that literally I mean it looks like
me in these videos and it's not perfect
like not all of them do. I created a
sequence of videos
uh where I was like driving a car and
getting pulled over and thing. It was
kind of a tongue and cheek thing where
I'm like, you know, don't do this or you
might go to jail type of a thing.
Um, I created a likeness of me dancing.
I'm running away from Pikachu, stuff
like that. I got coaching videos.
Okay, so Sora is incredible when it
comes to creating AI videos. And right
now, it is invite only. I have like
three invite codes right now. I'm kind
of reserving it for my inner circle. If
I can release more of them out to people
publicly, I will. Um, but here's one of
my recommendations for you. I actually
got my invite code. Um, I might get in
trouble for saying this, but that's
okay. Uh, by going to uh eBay,
and that's what I did. I literally typed
in uh Soratu invite. And listen, I can't
vouch for all of these. Uh, but I found
one for like 10 bucks. Uh, and I got the
code sent to me. Now, from what I
understand, every new account gets about
I think like four. I actually got eight
invites uh that I could send out to
people. And um I sent my like four out
and then they gave me four more. And so
that's what people are doing is
basically they're creating an account
then flipping these on eBay and selling
them. But if you don't know anybody who
has a code, I'd say 10 bucks is actually
worth it to get currently like unlimited
access to Sora. You might be watching
this in the future and you don't have to
worry about that type of a thing. Now,
when you first load up Sora, it has this
tool that
um it's called Cameo. When you create an
account, it'll basically have you go in
a well a well-lit room and on your
phone, you want to use your iPhone or
Android. I'm not sure if it's on
Android, but it might it might not be
with the Sora app. And what it does is
it does this thing called cameo. And you
can change your cameo.
You can add more people to your Cameo. I
could literally do one with my mom. I
could create one with my mom and a
friend. And I can even like bring
celebrities into it. The idea behind a
Cameo is
it does a it does a a scan of your face.
It has you like move your face left and
right. And I think it probably uses the
like the LAR that's on the camera to
really get like a representation of your
face. It has you record some audio.
Literally, you're just saying a couple
of words and then it can literally
duplicate your voice and visual. You
have control over it. By the way, you
have control over who can use it and
things like that. Now, we've been doing
this with a lot of different tools.
There's been different tools that I've
been teaching people how to use on my
YouTube. I've been talking about this.
One of my favorites is called Higsfield
AI. Higsfield AI is a video and image
generation app that I've been loving
using
because you can load up photos of
yourself and create identical images of
yourself
in any scene that you want and then turn
it into videos
uh using Higsfield. Okay, so Higsfield
and for the price is just one of the
best tools that's out there for creating
incredible
uh clones of yourself, digital twins,
for images. Uh but Sora literally
changed the game as far as for digital
twin videos because they look identical
to
I mean to you now. Some of the body
language is a little bit off. some of
the some of the the text and stuff like
that. But like it's it's it's so good
for for this tool to be able to do this
with Sora that it's hard to recommend
using other tools simply because Sora is
so advanced in its ability to do this.
You can scroll the feed in Sora and see
this.
They're what they're building is they're
building with Sora like kind of like a
Tik Tok competitor type of a thing. So
again, if you can get access to Sora,
that's the one that I would use for AI
videos just bar none. We've already been
using it for advertisements. We're
promoting an offer right now uh with my
mom's business and we created two. One
where she's jumping on a horse right
here
and she tells people that the price is
going up of her program. This is all AI
generated with Sora right here. The
price goes up. We added some text over
it. We did another one with her jumping
out of an airplane. My mom jumping out
of an airplane
uh using Sora. I mean, it's just it from
an advertising perspective, you can grab
people's attention quickly.
And for coaches especially, you can
create any scene. Um, one thing that I
do is I created multiple scenes and
actually strung them together even. And
this is another thing that I've been
playing around with Google Drive.
So, this I've been doing all this on my
phone, most of it, where I'll prompt it
and then I'll bring it into like a like
a video editing app. One of my favorites
is called InShot.
Um, it's called InShot right there. I n
o T. Cuz then I can easily just kind of
add my videos in here, edit them
together, string them together, and do
that. But I want to show you how I was
able to string together like a series of
videos to create a semi- tongue-in-cheek
uh video that I thought was funny. Um
funny slash not so funny slash just a
crazy representation of how AI is is
working um using this. And I'll and I'll
show you show this to you right here.
Let me see if I can load this up.
>> No laws were broken to create this
video. This is entire Here it is.
video. This is entirely made with AI.
>> Get in. We're making AI videos. Great
again.
>> That's illegal.
>> You know why I pulled you over today,
sir?
>> No, I don't. Officer,
>> don't try this at home or you'll end up
here.
>> Seriously, don't try it. But use Sora
for your AI videos.
So, I what I did was I prompted each
scene separately and then I was able to
edit them together into kind of a a
really interesting use case for AI. I'm
going to go post that tomorrow on my
social media. Um, where I'm like, "Okay,
the first scene I'm here outside of a a
police department in an orange
jumpsuit." Uh, and then I actually
prompted a countdown video with police
lights right here. I prompted uh me
pulling up in a Corvette. I prompted me
in the Corvette saying, "We're making AI
videos great again." And I prompted the
Corvette pulls away. I prompted uh
police body cam footage of me getting
pulled over in a Corvette.
Um and then I prompted me turning back
to the camera and winking, which is a
little creepy, but it works. Uh and then
I prompted me in a jail cell saying,
"Don't try this at home or you might end
up here."
So, those were all separate Sora videos
that I created. You can actually see
that inside of my Sora account that I
did this, but it only it only took me
like maybe 10 15 minutes to put them
together because the prompting is so
good. It's built by OpenAI and I I
believe they're using the chat GPT
engine behind it to come up with what
each scene is going to look like. So, I
kind of created like multiple versions
of each scene
um just because like the first ones did
not come out great. So, I what I what I
would do is I would prompt it multiple
times
once you have a video.
Um, you can click uh edit
and actually they don't they don't have
it on the on the app on the computer but
on the
on the phone
you can actually click on any video and
then click
edit. So like if I go to Sora and I
generated a video
I can quickly generate multiple versions
of it by like going okay here let me
just pull this up for you here. I'll
click on the video.
>> Don't try this at home or
>> I'll click on edit video. It'll pull up
my original prompt and then I just press
submit again and it'll literally submit
another draft version of it right there.
So that's how I was able to quickly
create multiple versions which is really
really cool. Um so yeah, I'm telling you
Sora is is incredible. Like I said, some
of my other favorite uh apps that are
out there, Higsfield Soul is really
cool. Um, the ability to create
characters and and and put that together
as well is just phenomenal. Uh, using
using Higsfield.
Um, you can create videos with
Higsfield.
Um, like we created, let's see, some of
these Higsfield soul images right here.
So, yes, like there's me getting out of
an airplane. So, like the quality on
these are really good.
Um, I would be eager to maybe create an
image in here and then pull it into Sora
and then prompt Sora to create the rest
of the scene. Right now, I don't think
that that's pos necessarily possible.
Uh, but I think it will be in the
future. And so, we were able to prompt
stuff like this.
You can then go in and you can create uh
videos. I created videos of me talking
right here.
Um, walking on a beach talking
uh walking forward and talking.
And then you can use um they have
a tool called lip sync which has talking
avatars.
>> Okay. So I'm not actually on a private
jet today. This is my AI clone on the
jet for me. Comment clone and I'll send
you a YouTube video.
>> So this is just Clling's uh the Cling
uh lip sync engine.
>> I love creating a
>> That one didn't come out good. This one
I love the cling videos.
>> I love creating AI videos that are
clones of me and I don't even have to
record on camera.
>> Okay, so that that one was created using
uh Clling and Higsfield and all of that.
Like I said, Sora is obviously superior
in quality
cuz they look so lifelike.
Even the body language like is cracking
me up how like it's actually like like
not all of them are but some of them are
literally like my body language. It's
very crazy. Kind of freaky.
Um
Higsfield has a lot of different tools
and stuff like that, but it's a little
more clunky compared to how Sora is.
Another really cool tool Labs.
Um you can use 11 Labs to clone your
voice for instance. I've I've been using
this to do uh voice clone versions of
myself. They have a a a version that I I
found called Voice Changer, which is
really cool, where I could actually
upload the voice audio from
uh say
Sora if it doesn't sound exactly like
me.
And then I can have 11 Labs generate a
different audio version using my voice
clone in here.
So, like my voice clone allows me to
generate audio cloned versions of
myself.
>> I love creating AI videos that are
clones of me and I don't even have to
record on camera.
>> Yeah. So, those are really really cool
and the quality is exceptional
um
with with generating uh audio.
And so, like in the past, something like
Higsfield, this is where it's it's kind
of clunky. You you bring the audio in
with an image. You generate an image
using Hfield Sold. Then you generate a
video and then you lip sync your video
to an audio. Um there's also Cling
Studio can do a lot of this as well.
Um you can do this inside of Cling
Studio right here. There's also Runway
ML. Runway ML. This cling and runway ML
are a little more advanced on this, but
the idea is is like these create Whoops,
that's not Runway ML. Um, the real
version of Runway ML is right here.
These are like AI film making tools and
and I'll tell you the quality of them is
exceptional uh when you start using them
and start playing around with them, but
they just they take a while to put
together. And so keep that in mind.
Keep that in mind that that
is something that you're going to want
to be able to do
if you want to create like advanced
level videos and stuff like that. But
again, I'm telling you, for for most of
you, using Sora is where it's at. Sora
is going to get you 90% of what you're
wanting to do with AI video. Yes, it has
the watermark on it. Yes, it's not
perfection quality, but I'm going tell
you taking 10 seconds to create a clip
in Sora
for me beats a 2hour workflow using
Runway or Higsfield or uh something like
that. So again, go get an invite, go
grab one. There's a ton of people
selling theirs on eBay. Maybe at the
time of watching this later, you won't
need to get one off of eBay and start
using it. It's incredible. All right,
we'll talk soon.
[Music]
[Applause]